Let me introduce you to some
new thangs new thangs new thangs
bass kick swingin' like I’m Bruce Lee
Bruce Lee Bruce Lee
shimmy shimmy shimmy I’m on fire on fire
shimmy shimmy shimmy api menyala-nyala saat
shimmy shimmy shimmy 火がつくのさ 火がつくのさ
shimmy shimmy shimmy Se enciende Se enciende
shimmy shimmy shimmy ไฟติดแล้ว ไฟติดแล้ว
shimmy shimmy shimmy 火力全開 火力全開
when I’m on this stage
aku berada di atas panggung
このステージに上がる時は
cuando este escenario flota para arriba
เมื่อขึ้นไปบนเวที
當我站上這舞台
I throw a straight punch right left Bruce Lee
Aku menyerang ke depan kiri dan kanan Bruce Lee
僕は前へ突く 左右 Bruce Lee
Apuñalo para adelante Bruce Lee
ตะโกนไปข้างหน้าและ รอบข้าง Bruce Lee
往左右揮出直拳 Bruce Lee
I’m flying around all day long Bruce Lee
terbang berkeliling seharian Bruce Lee
飛び回る 一日中 Bruce Lee
A la izquierda y la derecha vuelo todo el día Bruce Lee
ขึ้นไปทั้งวัน Bruce Lee
整天飛簷走壁 Bruce Lee
yeah yeah
comin' up here now
comin' up kemarilah sekarang
comin' up 今ここへ
comin' up Acá en este lugar
comin' up ที่นี่ ตอนนี้
Comin' up 現在來這裡
baby you don’t understand this feeling logically
baby kamu tak bisa melogika rasa ini
baby この感じは理解できない 頭では
baby No se comprende esta emoción con la cabeza
baby ความรู้สึกนี้ไม่อาจเข้าใจได้ด้วยเหตุผล
baby 你無法用腦袋理解這感覺
fighting for all day
Don’t think and walk along the path that leads to your story
jangan banyak berpikir terus melangkah sesuai ceritamu
何も考えずに君の話のままに歩いて
Sin pensar en nada camina con tu historia
ไม่ต้องคิดอะไร จงเดินไปตามเรื่องราวของเธอ
別想太多 照你的故事去走
Before the dark yesterday swallows today
Sebelum kegelapan kemarin menelan hari ini
暗い昨日が今日を飲みこんでしまう前に
Antes de que el oscuro ayer se trague el presente
ก่อนที่ความมืดมนของเมื่อวานจะปกคลุมวันนี้
在黑暗的昨日吞噬今天之前
My voice should spread more I can just shout out
Suaraku harus lebih menggema, maka berteriaklah
僕の声はもっと響かなきゃ 叫べばいい
Mi voz debe más lejos extenderse Hay que gritar
เสียงของฉันจะต้องดังกึกก้อ แค่ฉันตะโกน
我的聲音要擴散出去 大喊就行
To me no more trauma
Untukku no more trauma
僕には no more trauma
Para mí no more trauma
สำหรับฉัน no more trauma
我心中 no more trauma
Baby we go wild
one two seven squad
I throw a straight punch pow
Aku menyerang ke depan pow
僕は前へ突く pow
Grito para Adelante pow
ฉันจะตะโกนไปข้างหน้า pow
我往前揮拳 pow
Punch right and left pow
Ke samping kiri dan kanan pow
左右へ蹴飛ばす pow
Para los costados grito pow
ตะโกนไปรอบข้าง pow
往左右揮拳 pow
I throw a straight punch right and left
Aku menyerang ke depan kiri dan kanan
僕は前へ突く 左右
Apuñalo para Adelante A la izquierda y a la derecha
ฉันจะตะโกนไปข้างหน้าและ รอบข้าง
我往左右揮出直拳
new thangs new thangs new thangs
Wherever we go it’s a party
Kemanapun kita pergi ini adalah festival,
僕らがどこへ行こうがお祭りさ
Donde sea que vayamos se celebra
ไม่ว่าเราไปที่ไหนที่นั่นจะเป็นดั่งเทศกาล
我們到哪都是盛會
raise your glass and toast like my birthday
angkat gelasmu dan bersulang like my birthday
挙げよう祝杯を like my birthday
Arriba las copas a brindar like my birthday
ดื่มฉลอง like my birthday
舉杯慶祝 like my birthday
Everyone kicks up high
Semua tendang tinggi ke atas
皆 蹴り上げよう 高く
Todos envueltos lo pateo
เก็บทุกอย่างและขึ้น ไปให้สูง
所有人縱身往高空一踢
where ma roof at
roof in the universe (na na na na na na)
ke atap semesta (na na na na na na)
屋根が宇宙に (na na na na na na)
Al universo alto se va el techo (na na na na na na)
บนหลังคากาแล็กซี่ (na na na na na na)
屋頂在宇宙 (na na na na na na)
I throw a straight punch right and left Bruce Lee
Aku menyerang ke depan kiri dan kanan Bruce Lee
僕は前へ突く 左右 Bruce Lee
Apuñalo para Adelante A la izquierda y a la derecha Bruce Lee
ฉันจะตะโกนไปข้างหน้าและ รอบข้าง Bruce Lee
往左右揮出直拳 Bruce Lee
I’m flying around all day long Bruce Lee
terbang berkeliling seharian Bruce Lee
飛び回る 一日中 Bruce Lee
vuelo todo el día Bruce Lee
บินขึ้นไปทั้งวันBruce Lee
整天飛簷走壁 Bruce Lee
(na na na na na na)
(Ya!) got that drip Guts overflow
(Ya!) got that drip meluap Guts
(Ya!) got that drip あふれこぼれる Guts
(Ya!) got that drip Rebalsa Guts
(Ya!) got that drip ปล่อยออกมา Guts
(Ya!) got that drip 滿滿的 Guts
I lost fear
hilangnya rasa takut
なくした恐れ
El miedo olvidado
ความกลัวที่หายไป
膽怯不見蹤影
Wherever make it poppin' keep it movin' like ‘Jeet Kune’
Dimanapun make it poppin' keep it movin' like ‘Jeet Kune’
どこでも make it poppin' keep it movin' like ‘Jeet Kune’
Donde sea make it poppin' keep it movin' like ‘Jeet Kune’
ไม่ว่าจะที่ไหน make it poppin' keep itmovin' like ‘JeetKune’
不管在哪 make it poppin' keep it movin' like ‘Jeet Kune’
When you block me you’re gonna be ‘Samuel Jackson’ wassup?
Saat jalanku terhambat ‘Samuel Jackson’ pun wassup?
僕の行く手を阻む時は ‘Samuel Jackson’になる wassup?
Cuando tratan de pararme ‘Samuel Jackson’ wassup?
เมื่อมาขวางหน้าฉัน ‘Samuel Jackson’ ไง wassup?
你擋我的路 就會變‘Samuel Jackson’ wassup?
You’re so twisted baby you just gotta watch
Sangat gila baby you just gotta watch
ひねくれた奴 baby you just gotta watch
Qué retorcido eres tú baby you just gotta watch
คนที่วุ่นวาย baby you just gotta watch
肢體扭曲的傢伙 baby you just gotta watch
'Enter The Dragon' like a movie
'Enter The Dragon' bagai di film
‘Enter The Dragon' 僕は映画みたいに
'Enter The Dragon' Como en una película
'Enter The Dragon' เหมือนกับในหนัง
'Enter The Dragon' 我就像這部電影
Even my steps Martial Arts
Sampai langkahku pun Martial Arts
歩き方まで Martial Arts
Hasta como camino Martial Arts
แม้แต่ท่าทางการเดิน Martial Arts
步步都是Martial Arts
looking that everybody looking at me
Cams Action Movie shh
Knock down one by one
Jatuhkan satu per satu
なぎ倒せ ひとりずつ
Los tiro abajo uno a uno
ค่อยๆ ล้มมันไปทีละอย่าง
一個個擊倒
(Shh) blows away there’s no mercy ruthless
(Sst) blows away tanpa ampun ruthless
(シーッ) blows away 慈悲はないさ ruthless
(Sh) blows away Sin misericordia ruthless
(ชู่) blows away ไร้ความปราณี ruthless
(噓) blows away 手下不留情 ruthless
droppin' the bomb on ma enemies
and I’m gonna kick it like Bruce Lee
After repeating the same scenes of so many days
Akhir dari banyaknya hari dengan adegan berulang
数多くの日々の同じシーンを繰り返した果てに
Después de repetir imágenes iguales de innumerables días
บทสรุปของเรื่องราวที่ซ้ำไปซ้ำมาเหมือนเดิมในหลายวัน
經過無數個日子 重複同樣的畫面
I can just knock yesterday’s me down and shout out
Hancurkan dirimu yang kemarin dan berteriaklah
昨日の自分を倒して叫べばいい
Tiro abajo mi ser del pasado y grito
ทิ้งความเป็นตัวของฉันเมื่อวานแล้วตะโกนออกไป
我只要打倒昨天的我 大喊就好
To me no more trauma
Untukku no more trauma
僕には no more trauma
Para mí no more trauma
สำหรับฉัน no more trauma
我心中 no more trauma
Baby we go wild
one two seven squad
we ain’t never gonna stop
Even if we can’t see the end, just go
Walau ujung tak terlihat, tetap maju
終わりが見えなくても行く
Aunque no vea el fin, voy
ไปต่อถึงแม้จะไม่เห็นปลายทาง
看不見盡頭也照走
I throw a straight punch right left
Aku menyerang ke depan kiri dan kanan
僕は前へ突く 左右
Apuñalo para Adelante A la izquierda y a la derecha
ฉันจะตะโกนไปข้างหน้าและ รอบข้าง
我往左右揮出直拳
new thangs new thangs new thangs (na na na na na na)
I throw a straight punch right left Bruce Lee
Aku menyerang ke depan kiri dan kanan Bruce Lee
僕は前へ突く 左右 Bruce Lee
Apuñalo para Adelante A la izquierda y a la derecha Bruce Lee
ฉันจะตะโกนไปข้างหน้าและ รอบข้าง Bruce Lee
往左右揮出直拳 Bruce Lee
I’m flying around all day long Bruce Lee
terbang berkeliling seharian Bruce Lee
飛び回る 一日中 Bruce Lee
vuelo todo el día Bruce Lee
บินขึ้นไปทั้งวันBruce Lee
整天飛簷走壁 Bruce Lee
(na na na na na na)
I make my world yeah
my world terwujud yeah
my world 作ってゆく yeah
my world Voy creando yeah
my world สร้างขึ้นมา yeah
My world 我自己創造 yeah
Deep inside the very dramatic scene
Di dalam suasana yang sangat dramatis yang tidak terbayangkan
想像すらできなかった
Imágenes dramáticas imposibles de imaginar
ราวกับละครที่ไม่สามารถแม้แต่จะจินตนาการ
誰都沒辦法想像
that was unimaginable
とても劇的なシーン その深いところに
在極度戲劇化的畫面深處
En ese profundo lugar
The new worlds that will spread in front of me
目の前で繰り広げられる新しい世の中たち
Mundos que veré con mis ojos
โลกใบใหม่ที่อยู่ต่อหน้าฉัน และสามารถจับต้องมันได้
在眼前鋪展的嶄新世界
Dunia baru terpampang di depan mata,
will come into me as if I can grab them
masuk dalam diriku seakan aku bisa menggapainya
手でつかめるかのように僕の中へ入ってくる
Como si los pudiera tocar entran en mí
และสามารถจับต้องมันได้
將來到我身邊 彷彿伸手便能抓住
After the darkness I’m born again
Di akhir kegelapan, aku terlahir kembali
暗闇の果てに再び僕は生まれ変わる
Al final de la oscuridad vuelvo a nacer
ปลายทางของความมืดมน ฉันได้เกิดใหม่อีกครั้ง
我在黑暗的盡頭獲得新生
I throw a straight punch right and left
Aku menyerang ke depan kiri dan kanan
僕は前へ突く 左右
Apuñalo para Adelante A la izquierda y a la derecha
ฉันจะตะโกนไปข้างหน้าและรอบข้าง
我往左右揮出直拳
new thangs new thangs new thangs
Wherever we go it’s a party
Kemanapun kita pergi festival
僕らがどこへ行こうがお祭りさ
Donde sea que vayamos se celebra
ไม่ว่าเราไปที่ไหนที่นั่นจะเป็นดั่งเทศกาล
我們到哪都是盛會
raise your glass like my birthday (eh eh eh eh eh eh)
angkat bersulang like my birthday (eh eh eh eh eh eh)
挙げよう祝杯を like my birthday (eh eh eh eh eh eh)
Arriba las copas a brindar like my birthday (eh eh eh eh eh eh)
ดื่มฉลอง like my birthday (eh eh eh eh eh eh)
舉杯慶祝 like my birthday (eh eh eh eh eh eh)
shimmy shimmy shimmy catching fire
shimmy shimmy shimmy api menyala
shimmy shimmy shimmy 火がふっと
shimmy shimmy shimmy Fuego ju
shimmy shimmyshimmyไฟลุก ฟู่
shimmy shimmy shimmy 熊熊燃燒
shimmy shimmy shimmy hook
shimmy shimmy shimmy menyala
shimmy shimmy shimmy ふっと
shimmy shimmy shimmy ju
shimmy shimmyshimmy ฟู่
shimmy shimmy shimmy hook
High where ma roof at
Tinggi where ma roof at
高く where ma roof at
Al universo where ma roof at
สูงอีก where ma roof at
往高空 Where ma roof at
roof in the universe (na na na na na na)
ke atap semesta (na na na na na na)
屋根が宇宙に (na na na na na na)
alto se va el techo (na na na na na na)
บนหลังคากาแล็กซี่ (na na na na na na)
屋頂在宇宙 (na na na na na na)
I throw a straight punch right left Bruce Lee
Aku menyerang ke depan kiri dan kanan Bruce Lee
僕は前へ突く 左右 Bruce Lee
Apuñalo para Adelante A la izquierda y a la derecha Bruce Lee
ฉันจะตะโกนไปข้างหน้า และรอบข้าง Bruce Lee
往左右揮出直拳 Bruce Lee
I’m flying around all day long Bruce Lee (na na na na na na)
terbang berkeliling seharian Bruce Lee (na na na na na na)
飛び回る 一日中 Bruce Lee
Vuelo todo el día Bruce Lee (na na na na na na)
บินขึ้นไปทั้งวันBruce Lee (na na na na na na)
整天飛簷走壁 Bruce Lee (na na na na na na)
I’m flying around all day long Bruce Lee
Terbang berkeliling seharian Bruce Lee
飛び回る 一日中 Bruce Lee
Vuelo todo el día Bruce Lee
ขึ้นไปทั้งวันBruce Lee
整天飛簷走壁 Bruce Lee